<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Zxus</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Zxus</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.133.1</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:32:51 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Huffman Coding</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/huffman-coding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 17:32:51 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/huffman-coding/</guid>
      <description>Huffman Coding Huffman Coding is a popular algorithm used for data compression. It was developed by David A. Huffman in 1952 as part of his research on finding the most efficient binary code. Huffman Coding is widely used because of its simplicity and effectiveness in reducing data size without losing information.
Table of Contents Introduction How Huffman Coding Works Example of Huffman Coding Decoding with Huffman Code Advantages of Huffman Coding Applications of Huffman Coding Limitations of Huffman Coding Introduction Huffman Coding is a lossless compression algorithm, meaning no data is lost during the compression process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Git Submodules</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/git-submodules/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 22:26:49 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/git-submodules/</guid>
      <description>Embracing Git Submodules: A Journey to a Seamless Dotfiles Setup I had been using stow since it was simple, but I was tired of making countless number of directories. I believed there had to be a better way. and oh boy, yadm it was. In my quest towards a perfect dotfiles setup in my Arch Linux and Neovim PDE (btw), Git submodules turned out to be hero I needed but not deserved.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Aug 2024 19:30:47 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Introduction This is bold text, and this is emphasized text.
Visit the Hugo website!</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
